Melinda Dienes

47 Hibbert Road London HA3 7JU

① 07719682420



Personal profile

Having years of experience in hospitality I'm customer focused, welcoming, friendly and approachable for clients and team members as well. I'm adaptable to sudden changes and demonstrate willingness when facing unforeseen situations. I step up to challenges when working independently also efficiently and effectively on my own.

Professional experience

March 2019 - Present

Front of House Assistant

February 2018 – Dec. 2018 Cluster Reservations Agent

Sept. 2017 – February 2018 Front of House Supervisor

Sept. 2016 – Sept. 2017 Receptionist - Front of House

ISS Facility Services Limited

Currently I'm taking care of the Front of House duties, including administration, stock take, and managing the booking system and requirements.

Hilton London Tower Bridge

I worked efficiently in a fast-paced office where clients appreciated contacting me as I offered good customer service.

I analysed all guest, travel agent requirements via telephone, emails and recommended suitable options and other solutions to meet the customer needs. I offered room packages and made reservations to maximise revenue.

I confirmed the reservations and ensured every booking details are updated.

Hilton London Olympia

I supervised the Front Desk operations during the shift, and I oversaw the front office activities between the Guest, the hotel, and the various hotel departments. I ensured the team have good knowledge of the hotel products, services, pricing, and special promotions to motivate them maximizing sales revenues through up-sells. and as a Hilton Honors Champion I motivated them for the enrolment as well to achieve and exceed the monthly target.

Hilton London Olympia

I provided an efficient reception experience for guests, including check in/out. I responded to inquiries as I am familiar with the selling status, rates, and benefits of packages. I made reservations, as well as processed cancellations and modifications. I understood the hotel's policy on guaranteed reservations and no-shows and I kept track on room availability on the basis of reservations. I prepared and sent letters of confirmations and invoices to our clients as well.

January 2016 – Sept. 2016

Team Leader

Sept. 2011 – Dec. 2015

Food & Beverage Assistant

Hilton London Angel Islington

I managed the shift efficiently and effectively, followed up on e-mails and administration. Also I made sure every guest requests/complains are looked after. I took care of the bookings by phone and updated them on the website. I made sure the restaurant has enough supplies in stock to run it efficiently by ordering the necessary items. I delegated tasks to the team on morning briefings and I provided training for them as well.

Hilton London Angel Islington

Task range from hosting, follow cash handling procedures, and comply with local licensing laws and strive to achieve departmental targets.

Responsible for looking after guests and attending to their needs and customer satisfaction during their visit. Duties included preparation tasks preserving period and proactively attending customer expectations by delivering a high standard of service.

Achievements

Hilton Honors Champion

Costa trainer & auditor

"Catch me at my best"

Story of the Month

Employee of the Month

Responsible for Hilton Honors enrolments, training the team of HH benefits

Nominated trainer by the Restaurant Manager

First place for the best customer service

Creating new menu for the Restaurant 2015/2016

Three times in 2011, 2013, 2014 and 2018 for flexibility and prioritising what is most important, consistently delivering results, offering supervisory supporting to the team, dedication and team support

Key skills

- ➤ **Leadership:** motivator, team-builder, confidence booster, visionary
- ➤ **Team-work spirit:** Supportive, organised, co-ordinator, deliverer, openminded
- > Interpersonal skills: Trainer, communicator, empathetic, listener, adviser, professional, co-operative, assertive, tactful, diplomatic, tolerant
- ➤ Customer service & customer care skill: welcoming, accommodating, friendly, approachable

Education	
2016	Personal Licence Training BIIAB Level 2 Award for Personal Licence Holders
2015	Photography Institute Photographer
	Costa Academy Barista
2011	International Crew Ship Training Centre Food & Beverage Assistant and Language course
2004-2006	University of Szeged – Faculty of Food-industry College Food Industry Manager, Entrepreneurial
2002-2004	Food-industry and Surveying High School GCSE
IT user skills	
OnQPM and Micros	Reservation and Invoicing System
Programming	Microsoft Word, Excel, Power Point, Outlook
Language skills	
Hungarian	Native
English	Fluent (written and spoken)
German	Beginner